wysiwygwebbuilder.com 2019-08-14

# Privacy Policy

**WYSIWYG Web Builder - Privacy Policy** **Personal Information** **  
**When you buy a license for WYSIWYG Web Builder, your payment will be handled by one of our resellers Avangate or MyCommerce.  
They will pass some of your information to us, such as your IP address, name, email address and postal address.   
Resellers do not share credit card or other payment information with us. 

MyCommerce/Digital River Privacy Policy   
<https://www.digitalriver.com/corporate-policies/>

Avangate/2checkout Privacy Policy   
<http://www.avangate.com/legal/privacy.php>

From the order information, only your email address and serial number will be stored so that we can set up an account in the registered users area (for downloading extensions and other extras), resend your license information if you lose it and check your eligibility for upgrades. 

We also collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail or forms on the website to helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests.

Any information collected from you will not be sold, rented or disclosed in any way to any third parties. 

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies** **  
**This website only uses cookie for the forum. Please see the privacy policy of the forum for more information:  
<http://wysiwygwebbuilder.com/forum/ucp.php?mode=privacy>

We do not use Google Analytics or other analytics services.

 **Your data** **  
**WYSIWYG Web builder is a desktop app, so all your data (projects, HTML, CSS, JS, images etc.) is stored your computer, nothing is stored on our servers.  
When you are contacting us for support we may ask you to send your project file so we can assist you more efficiently. This data will be deleted when the issue has been resolved. **Contacting You** **  
**We will not use your email address to send unsolicited messages.  
We may send a (one-time) upgrade discount offer to licensed users of WYSIWYG Web Builder when a new major version has been released. You can decide not to receive emails from us and unsubscribe from the upgrade notification list via the 'unsubscribe' link in that email. 

We reserve the right to change, modify or update this statement at any time without notice.
